Genetics Society of America Records 1921-1982 Mss.575.06.G28p
American Philosophical Society
- Genetics Society of America Records, 1921-1984; 24.5 Linear feet 24.5 lin. feet
  - Records, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1947; 9 folders (Box 4)
      - Transportation Committee, 8th International Congress, 1947 (Box 4)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Happ, George B, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Hazel, L N, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Human Genetics Society of America, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Hunt, H R, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Huxley, Julian S, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Indiana University, 1947 (Box 4)
    - International Commission on Zoological Nomenclature, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Inter-Society Commission on a National Science Foundation, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Karling, John S, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Kitzmiller, James B, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Landauer, Walter, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Lindstrom, E W, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Lush, Jay L, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Mac Arthur, John W, 1947 (Box 4)
    - McClintock, Barbara, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Marshak, Albert, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Mello, Raul G, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Metz, C W, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Micro-Photography Co., 1947 (Box 4)
    - Missouri Pacific Lines, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Mittler, Sidney, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Monsanto Chemical Co., 1947 (Box 4)
    - Morris, M Rosalind, 1947 (Box 4)
    - Muller, H.J., 1947; 5 folders (Box 4)
    - National Research Council, 1947; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Neel, James V, 1947 (Box 5)
    - New York Convention & Visitors Bureau, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Ontario Agricultural College, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Raybourne, R C, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Reynolds, Paul J, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Rickey, F D, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Science, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Scientific Monthly, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Scientific Personnel Bulletin, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Scott, J P, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Singleton, W Ralph, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Snyder, Laurence H, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Society for the Study of Evolution, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Stern, Curt, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Stevens Hotel, Chicago, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Stone, Wilson S, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Strandskov, Herluf H, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Texas Agricultural Experiment Station, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Weir, J R, 1947 (Box 5)
    - Wright, Sewall, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Records, 1948 (Box 5)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1948 (Box 5)
    - American Genetic Association, 1948 (Box 5)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1948; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - American Men of Science, 1948 (Box 5)
    - American Society of Naturalists, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Associated Press, 1948 (Box 5)
    - G. Banta Pub. Co., 1948 (Box 5)
    - Beadle, G W, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Biological Abstracts, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Colin, Edward C, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Committee of the International Shows, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Cushing-Malloy Inc., 1948 (Box 5)
    - Demerec, M, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Dunn, L C, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Edwards Brothers Inc., 1948 (Box 5)
    - Emsweller, S L, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Ephrussi, Boris, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Everett, H L, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Fulbright Act., 1948 (Box 5)
    - Glass, H Bently, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Gowen, John W, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1948; 9 folders (Box 5)
      - Committee on Aid to Geneticists Abroad, 1948 (Box 5)
      - Constitution & By-Laws, 1948 (Box 5)
      - Executive Committee, 1948 (Box 5)
      - Membership Records, 1948 (Box 5)
      - Nominating Committee, 1948 (Box 5)
      - Travel Fund, 1948 (Box 5)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1948; 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Hansen, Ira B, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Happ, George B, 1948 (Box 5)
    - Heston, W E, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Human Genetics Society of America, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Iltis, Hugo, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Karling, John S, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Kaufmann, B P, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Komai, Taku, 1948 (Box 6)
    - C. Laughlin Travel Service, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Lindstrom, E W, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Little, C C, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Mello, Raul F, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Muller, H J, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Oak Ridge National Labs, 1948 (Box 6)
    - National Research Council, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Reed, Sheldon, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Rife, David C, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Rubin, B A, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Sears, E R, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Shull, George H, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Snyder, Laurence H, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Sonneborn, T M, 1948; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Spencer, Beryl A, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Spuhler, J N, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Stadler, L J, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Steinback, H B, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Stephens, S G, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Stern, Curt, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Swanson, C P, 1948 (Box 6)
    - U.S. Army, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Whiting, P W, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Wolff, Harold Arnold, 1948 (Box 6)
    - Woolley, George W, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Records, 1949 (Box 6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1949 (Box 6)
    - American Institute of Biological Sci., 1949; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1949 (Box 6)
    - American Seed Trade Association, 1949 (Box 6)
    - American Society of Zoologists, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Banta Pub. Co., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Biological Abstracts, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Boswell, Victor R, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Botanical Congress, Seventh International, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Brown Pub. Co., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Cain, Stanley A, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Chambers, Robert, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1949 (Box 6)
    - C.O.T.E.C., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Cushing-Malloy Inc., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Demerec, M, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Draper, W P, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Dreyer, William A., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Dunn, L. C, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Edwards Brothers Inc., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Genetical Society of Great Britain, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Glass, Bentley, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Goldstein, Philip, 1949; 9 folders (Box 6)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Commission on Aid to Geneticists Abroad, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Commission to Combat Anti-Genetics Propaganda, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee, 1949; 2 folders (Box 6)
      - History of the Genetics Society of America, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Membership Recommendations, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Membership Records, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Minute Book, 1949 (Box 6)
      - Orders, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Haines, Mrs. George, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Hall, Benedict Mark, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Heyne, Elmer E, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Huxley, Julian, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Institute of Genetics, Stockholm, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Italian Society of Genetics & Eugenics, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Jenkins, M T, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Kaufmann, Berwind P, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Lambda Electronics Corp, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Lang, Anton, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Lange, Maxwell and Springer Ltd., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Lee, Roger I, 1949 (Box 6)
    - McClintock, Barbara, 1949 (Box 6)
    - McPhee, Hugh C, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Martinus, Nijhoff, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Mavor, James W, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Metz, C W, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Mirsky, A E, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Scientific American, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Singleton, W Ralph, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Sirks, M J, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Sonneborn, T M, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Stadler, L J, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Kurt, Staeheli & Co., 1949 (Box 6)
    - Stern, Curt, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Stone, Wilson S, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Stranshov, H L, 1949 (Box 6)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1949 (Box 6)
    - University of North Carolina, 1949 (Box 6)
    - Whiting, P W, 1949 (Box 6)
  - Records, 1950 (Box 6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1950 (Box 6)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1950; 5 folders (Box 6)
    - American Micriscopical Society, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Biological Abstracts, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1950 (Box 6)
    - Cushing-Malloy Inc., 1950 (Box 6)
    - Dempster, Everett R, 1950 (Box 6)
    - "The Gene and the Soviet Union", 1950 (Box 6)
    - Genetics in the Twentieth Century, 1950 (Box 6)
      L.C.Dunn ecitor
    - Golden Jubilee of Genetics, 1950; 30 folders (Box 6)
      Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Genetics; Genetics Society of America -- Golden Jubilee; History of biology, especially genetics; Publication
      - Correspondence (folders 1-5), 1950; 5 folders (Box 6)
      - Correspondence (folders 6-13), 1950; 8 folders (Box 7)
      - L.C.Dunn Correspondence, 1950; 3 folders (Box 7)
      - M.R. Irwin Correspondence, 1950; 5 folders (Box 7)
      - Local Representative, 1950; 3 folders (Box 7)
      - Publications, 1950; 4 folders (Box 7)
      - Publicity, 1950; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1950; 26 folders (Box 7)
      - Committee on Aid to Geneticists Abroad, 1950 (Box 7)
      - Committee on Public Education & Scientific Freedom, 1950 (Box 7)
      - Committee to Counteract Anti-Genetics Propaganda, 1950 (Box 7)
      - Executive Committee, 1950; 4 folders (Box 7)
      - Membership - Emeritus, 1950; 3 folders (Box 7)
      - Membership Records, 1950; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Newsletters, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Nominations, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Program Committee, 1950; 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Public Education and Scientific Freedom Committee, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Records, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Representatives of Society, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Sustaining Membership, 1950; 4 folders (Box 8)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Iltis, Hugo, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Irwin, M. R., 1950 (Box 8)
    - National Research Council, 1950 (Box 8)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1950 (Box 8)
  - Records, 1951 (Box 8)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1951 (Box 8)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1951; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - American Society of Naturalists, 1951 (Box 8)
    - A P Illistrated News Features, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Brink, R A, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Caspari, Ernst, 1951; 3 folders (Box 8)
    - Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Cushing-Malloy Inc., 1951 (Box 8)
    - Dunn, L C, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1951; 16 folders (Box 8)
      - Ballots, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Committee on Aid to Geneticists Abroad, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Committee on Public Education & Scientific Freedom, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Counselling, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Emeritus Members, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Executive Committee, 1951; 5 folders (Box 8)
      - Membership Recommendations, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Membership Records, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Minneapolis Meeting Committee, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Program Committee, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Records, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Representatives of the Society, 1951 (Box 8)
    - National Research Council, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Tschermak-Seysenegg, Erich von, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Records, 1952 (Box 9)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1952 (Box 9)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1952; 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Caspari, Ernst, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Clausen, Roy E, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Genetics, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Gowen, John W, 1952; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1952; 21 folders (Box 9)
      - Ballot, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Committee on Public Education & Scientific Freedom, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Executive Committee, 1952; 5 folders (Box 9)
      - Ithaca Meeting Committee, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Ithaca Meeting - Minutes, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Membership Records, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Newsletters, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Nominating Committee, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Program Committee, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Publications, 1952; 3 folders (Box 9)
      - Representatives of the Society, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Screening & Evaluating Committee - IX International Congress, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1952; 2 folders (Box 9)
      - Travel Committee, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Ninth International Congress on Genetics, 1952 (Box 9)
    - Oliver, Clarence P, 1952 (Box 9)
  - Records, 1953 (Box 10)
    - American Assocation for the Advancement of Science, 1953; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - American Cancer Society, 1953 (Box 10)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1953; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - American Journal of Botany, 1953 (Box 10)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1953 (Box 10)
    - American Society of Agronomy, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Anderson, Jacob P, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Boyd, William C, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Boyes, J W, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Caspari, Ernst, 1953; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - City College, N.Y., 1953 (Box 10)
    - Clausen, Roy E, 1953; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Collins, W M, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Cooperative Research Foundation, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Creighton, Harriet B, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Crow, James, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Demerec, M, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Dunn, Leslie Clarence, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Edwards, Marvin L, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Everett, H L, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Galinat, Walton C, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Genetics, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Goldsmith, William M, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Gowen, John W, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1953; 23 folders (Box 10)
      - Auditing Committee, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Ballots, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Boston Meeting, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Boston Meeting Committee, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Committee on Aid to Geneticists Abroad, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Committee on Public Education & Scientific Freedom, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Executive Committee, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Membership Records, 1953; 4 folders (Box 10)
      - Newsletters, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Nominating Committee, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Nominations, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Program Committee, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Publications, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Report of the Secretary, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Representatives of the Society, 1953 (Box 10)
      - Screening Committee, 1953 (Box 11)
      - Secretaty's Notes, 1953 (Box 11)
      - Travel Committee, 1953 (Box 11)
      - Travel Grants, 1953 (Box 11)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Hawthorne, Mary E, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Hollaender, Alexander, 1953 (Box 11)
    - House, Verl L, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Huskins, Charles Leonard, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Irwin, M R, 1953 (Box 11)
    - James, Allen P, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Kelner, Albert, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Lerner, I Michael, 1953 (Box 11)
    - MacIntosh, F C, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Meyer, James R, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Morgan, Lilian V, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Muller, H J, 1953 (Box 11)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1953 (Box 11)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Ninth International Congress on Genetics, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Ninth International Congress - Screening Committee, 1953; 8 folders (Box 11)
    - Newcomer, Earl H, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Pauley, Scott S, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Plough, H H, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Poulson, Donald F, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Public Health Service, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Rollins, Reed C, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Ross, James G, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Ryan, Francis, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Sax, Karl, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Schwartz, Drew, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Science Press, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Seaney, R R, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Sheraton Plaza, Boston, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Shull, George H, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Singleton, W R, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Sokal, Robert R, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Sonneborn, Tracy M, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Stern, Curt, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Swanson, C P, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Tazima, Yataro, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Tenth International Congress on Genetics, 1953 (Box 11)
    - University of California, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Wainwright, Stanley D, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Weizmann Institute of Science, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Whittinghill, Maurice, 1953 (Box 11)
  - Records, 1954 (Box 11)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1954 (Box 11)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1954; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Araneta Institute of Agriculture, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Battelle Memorial Institute, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Bhaerman, Robert, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Breth, Steven, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Brink, R A, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Carver, G L, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Caspari, Ernst, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Clausen, Roy E, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Cooperative Research Foundation, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Dickinson, J C, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Fox, Allen S, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Genetics, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Giles, Norman H, Jr., 1954 (Box 11)
    - Glass, Bentley, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Goldschmidt, Richard B, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Gowen, John W, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Grobman, Arnold, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1954; 14 folders (Box 11)
      - Biographical Sketches, 1954 (Box 11)
      - Executive Committee, 1954 (Box 11)
      - Membership Nominations, 1954 (Box 11)
      - Genetics Society of America - Membership Records, 1954; 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Newsletters, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Nominating Committee, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Program Committee, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Public Education & Scientific Freedom Committee, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Representatives of the Society, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Twenty-third Annual Meeting, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Hecht, Adolph, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Herskowitz, Irwin H, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Heyne, E G, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Hull, Fred H, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Hunt, H R, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Hutt, F B, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Hyde, Beal B, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Instituto de Nutrition De Centro America y Panama, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Irwin, M R, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Italian Society of Agrarian Genetics, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Jaffe, Frieda, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Johns, Charley E (Acting Gov.,Florida), 1954 (Box 12)
    - Kerns, Kenneth, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Koger, Marvin, 1954 (Box 12)
    - L & A Railway Lines, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Mendel Museum of Genetics, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Meyer, James R, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Mickey, George H, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Miller, Dwight D, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Morrison, J W, 1954 (Box 12)
    - National Research Council, 1954 (Box 12)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Owen, Ray D, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Patterson, J T, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Public Administration Clearing House, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Ratty, Frank J, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Romer, Alfred S, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Ryan, Francis J, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Saez, F A, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Schwartz, Drew, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Science Press, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Shapard, Pauline B, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Singleton, W R, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Smith, S G, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Snyder, L H, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Stern, Curt, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Taschdjian, E, 1954 (Box 12)
    - Tenth International Congress on Genetics, 1954; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Records, 1955 (Box 12)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1955 (Box 12)
    - American Chemical Society, 1955 (Box 12)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1955; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Basic Book Service, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Baten, W D, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Benzer, Seymour, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Brewbaker, H E, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Bull, Alice Louise, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Burdick, Allan B, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Canadian National Railways, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Caspari, Ernst W, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Centro Appenninico, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Clausen, Roy E, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1955; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Colin, Edward, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Council for the Advancement of Negroes in Science, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Crow, James, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Ecological Society of America, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Emsweller, S L, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1955 (Box 12)
    - General Electrics Co., 1955 (Box 12)
    - Genetics, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Giles, Norman, 1955; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Glass, Bentley, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Gowen, John W, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1955; 19 folders (Box 12)
      - Biographical Sketches, 1955 (Box 12)
      - Committee on Smith College Genetics Experiment Station, 1955 (Box 12)
      - East Lansing Meeting, 1955; 5 folders (Box 13)
        - Local Committee, 1955 (Box 13)
        - Proceedings, 1955 (Box 13)
        - Program, 1955; 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Sewall Wright's Contribution to Population Genetics, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Executive Committee, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Genetics Society of America - Grant Committee, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Membership Records, 1955; 6 folders (Box 13)
      - Newsletters, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Nominating Committee, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Treasurer's Report, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Gunn Brothers Quail Farm, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Heinicke Instruments, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Herndon, C Nash, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Heyne, E G, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Hollaender, Alexander, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Immigration and Naturalization, 1955 (Box 13)
    - International Science Foundation, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Irwin, M R, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Italian Genetics Society, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Knott, D R, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Leonard, Warren H, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Luning, K G, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Lush, J L, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Mangelsdorf, Paul C, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Medical News, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Mehlquist, Gustau A L, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Mello, Raul F, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Mendel Museum of Genetics, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Muller, H J, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Myrick, Richard, 1955 (Box 13)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1955 (Box 13)
    - National Humane Society, 1955 (Box 13)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1955 (Box 13)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Nepera Chemical Co., 1955 (Box 13)
    - Newcombe, H B, 1955; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Paul, Julius, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Rhoades, M M, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Richey, Frederick D, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Ryan, Francis, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Science Museum Library, London, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Science Press, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Singleton, W Ralph, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Spencer, Warren P, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Tenth International Congress on Genetics, 1955; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - University of California, 1955 (Box 13)
    - University of California Press, 1955 (Box 13)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1955 (Box 13)
    - U.S. National Commission for UNESCO, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Waverly Press, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Wentworth, EdwardN, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Western Reserve University, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Wilson, G B, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Records, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Altenburg, Luolin & Edgar, 1956 (Box 14)
    - American Association for Advancement of Science, 1956; 4 folders (Box 14)
    - American Genetic Association, 1956 (Box 14)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1956; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - American Society of Naturalists, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Anderson, E G, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Barnett, Jerry, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Blummel, Hohanna, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Botanical Society of America, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Boyes, J Wallace, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Brink, R A, 1956; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Brown, Meta S, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Burris, Martin J, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Caspari, Ernst W, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Chovnick, Arthur, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1956; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Cook, Robert C, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Coronet Magazine, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Crow, James F, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Dawson, A B, 1956 (Box 14)
    - Dengler, Robert E, 1956 (Box 14)